Class of 1946 Records, 1942-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1946 Records
1942-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1946.
RG 80 UUID:fc985af9-9476-4fc6-8a13-0e53f8e9153d
4 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1946.
Historical Note
The Class of 1946 was the sixty-eighth graduating class of Smith College. As part of a war-time acceleration program, some members of the Class of 1946 graduated in August, 1945.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1946 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1946, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1946 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 1)
- Commencement-August 1945 (Box 2155, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Music 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Photographs 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 4)
- Ivy Day 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 5)
- Ivy Day 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1942-1943 (Box 2155, Folder 7)
- General 1943 (Box 2155, Folder 8)
- Groups 1942-1946 (Box 2155, Folder 9)
- Hoop Rolling 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 10)
- Class Letters 1967-2002 (Box 2155, Folder 11)
- Mountain Day 1942 (Box 2155, Folder 12)
- News Clippings n.d. (Box 2155, Folder 13)
- Officers 1942-1946 (Box 2155, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1951-1966 (Box 2155, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2155, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1976-1981 (Box 2155, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1991 (Box 2155, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1996 (Box 2155, Folder 19)
- Reunions-Newsletters 1996-2001 (Box 2155, Folder 20)
- Songs n.d. (Box 2155, Folder 21)
- Sophomore Carnival 1944 (Box 2155, Folder 22)
- Sophomore Push 1944 (Box 2155, Folder 23)
- Class Supper 1946 (Box 2155, Folder 24)
- Year Book n.d. (Box 2155, Folder 25)
- Reunion Book 1996 (Box 2155, Folder 26)